{"data":[{"question":"Whose bicycle is it? It's ________.","a":"he","b":"her","c":"hers","d":"she","answer":"3","explain":"- Hers: possessive pronoun of she,\u00a0hers = her bicycle","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"How old is ________?","a":"she","b":"her","c":"hers","d":"his","answer":"1","explain":"\n- He: a pronoun as the subject\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"There are ________ eggs on the table.","a":"some","b":"any","c":"many","d":"much","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Some: used for countable\/uncountable nouns","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Is there ________ cheese on the table?","a":"some","b":"any","c":"many","d":"much","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use any in questions","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"How ________ cakes does she want?","a":"some","b":"any","c":"many","d":"much","answer":"3","explain":"\n- How much + uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- How many + countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Peter doesn't want ________ eggs, but he wants some soup.","a":"some","b":"any","c":"many","d":"much","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Any: used in negative sentences","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"There is ________ milk in the glass.","a":"some","b":"any","c":"many","d":"much","answer":"1","explain":"- Some can be followed by uncountable\/countable nouns","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"How ________ meat do you want?","a":"some","b":"any","c":"many","d":"much","answer":"4","explain":"\n- How much + uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- How many + countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"There isn't ________ coffee in the cup.","a":"some","b":"any","c":"many","d":"much","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Any: used in questions and negative sentences","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They want ________ coffee, but they don't want any bread.","a":"some","b":"any","c":"many","d":"much","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Some + uncountable noun\/plural noun (use in narrative sentence).\u00a0\n- Any + uncountable noun\/plural noun (use in negative and question sentence).\u00a0\n- Many + countable + plural noun.\u00a0\n- Much + uncountable noun (mean a large amount of something).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}